Guide to the Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 1, Section 6: Boxes 111-121
Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 1, Section 6: Boxes 111-121
- Box: 114, Folder: 5 (Box 114, Folder 5)
  - Item 8: Report on a Decision of the Secretary of Labor Pursuant to Section 11 of Executive Order 10988 Report Number 7, Publication (Box 114, Folder 5)
    October 9. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Report on a Decision of the Secretary of Labor Pursuant to Section 11 of Executive Order 10988 Report Number 8, Publication (Box 114, Folder 5)
    December 10. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: Report on a Decision of the Secretary of Labor Pursuant to Section 11 of Executive Order 10988 Report Number 9, Publication (Box 114, Folder 5)
  - Item 11: Report on a Decision of the Secretary of Labor Pursuant to Section 11 of Executive Order 10988 Report Number 10, Publication (Box 114, Folder 5)
    December 18. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: Report on a Decision of the Secretary of Labor Pursuant to Section 11 of Executive Order 10988 Report Number 11, Publication (Box 114, Folder 5)
    January 27. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: Report on a Decision of the Secretary of Labor Pursuan tto Section 11 of Executive Order 10988 Report Number 12, Publication (Box 114, Folder 5)
    March 5. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: Report on a Decision of the Secretary of Labor Pursuant to Section 11 of Executive Order 10988, Publication (Box 114, Folder 5)
    August 7. Item is in English.
  - Item 15: Report on a Decision of the Secretary of Labor Pursuant to Section 11 of Executive Order 10988 Report Number 14, Publication (Box 114, Folder 5)
  - Item 16: Report on a Decision of the Secretary of Labor Pursuant to Section 11 of Executive Order 10988 Report Number 15, Publication (Box 114, Folder 5)
  - Item 17: Report on a Decision of the Secretary of Labor Pursuant to Section 11 of Executive Order 10988 Report Number 16, Publication (Box 114, Folder 5)
    June 22. Item is in English.
  - Item 18: Report on a Decision of the Secretary of Labor Pursuant to Section 11 of Executive Order 10988 Report Number 17, Publication (Box 114, Folder 5)
    July 12. Item is in English.
  - Item 19: Report on a Decision of the Secretary of Labor Pursuant to Section 11 of Executive Order 10988 Report Number 18, Publication (Box 114, Folder 5)
    September 27. Item is in English.
  - Item 20: Report on a Decision of the Secretary of Labor Pursuant to Section 11 of Executive Order 10988, Publication (Box 114, Folder 5)
    September 19. Item is in English.
  - Item 21: Report on a Decision of the Secretary of Labor Pursuant to Section 11 of Executive Order 10988 Report Number 20, Publication (Box 114, Folder 5)
    January 3. Item is in English.
  - Item 22: Report on a Decision of the Secretary of Labor Pursuant to Section 11 of Executive Order 10988 Report Number 22, Publication (Box 114, Folder 5)
    September 6. Item is in English.
  - Item 23: Report on a Decision of the Secretary of Labor Pursuant to Section 11 of Executive Order 10988 Report Number 21, Publication (Box 114, Folder 5)
    January 9. Item is in English.
  - Item 24: Report on a Decision of the Secretary of Labor Pursuant to Section 11 of Executive Order 10988 Report Number 23, Publication (Box 114, Folder 5)
  - Item 25: Report on a Decision of th eSecretary of Labor Pursuant to Section 11 of Executive Order 10988 Report Number 24, Publication (Box 114, Folder 5)
    October 31. Item is in English.
  - Item 26: Help us meet the challenge, Publication (Box 114, Folder 5)
  - Item 27: Policy and Procedures for Suitability Investigations, Publication (Box 114, Folder 5)
    November 17. Item is in English.
  - Item 28: Careers For Junior Management Assistants in the U.S. Department of Labor, Publication (Box 114, Folder 5)
  - Item 29: Position Classification, Publication (Box 114, Folder 5)
  - Item 30: Performance Requirements, Publication (Box 114, Folder 5)
  - Item 31: Quesetions and Answers Regarding the Federal Service Entrance Examination and Its Management Intern Option, Publication (Box 114, Folder 5)
  - Item 32: Procedural guide for Majority Status Determinations Under Section 11 of Executive Order 10988, Publication (Box 114, Folder 5)
  - Item 33: Procedural Guide For Advisory Arbitration Proceedings Under Section 11 of Executive Order 10988, Publication (Box 114, Folder 5)
  - Item 34: Rules For The Nomination of Arbitrators Under Section II of Executive Order 10988, As Amended, Publication (Box 114, Folder 5)
    August 14. Item is in English.
  - Item 35: Administration of Position Classification, Publication (Box 114, Folder 5)
  - Item 36: Administration of the Performance Rating Plan of the Department of Labor, Publication (Box 114, Folder 5)
    February 21. Item is in English.
  - Item 37: Notice to Users of Personnel Instruction No. 27, Publication (Box 114, Folder 5)
    January 20. Item is in English.
- Box: 114, Folder: 6 (Box 114, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: The Department of Labor, Publication (Box 114, Folder 6)
  - Item 2: Management Leadership, Publication (Box 114, Folder 6)
  - Item 3: Career Development Workshop, Publication (Box 114, Folder 6)
  - Item 4: Office Management and General Secretarial Functions Seminar, Publication (Box 114, Folder 6)
  - Item 5: U.S. Department of Labor Twenty-Five Years of Service 1913-1938, Publication (Box 114, Folder 6)
  - Item 6: Telephone Techniques and Etiquette, Publication (Box 114, Folder 6)
  - Item 7: Professional and Supervisory Program, Publication (Box 114, Folder 6)
  - Item 8: Effective Executive Writing, Publication (Box 114, Folder 6)
  - Item 9: Performance Appraisal, Publication (Box 114, Folder 6)
  - Item 10: Office Skills Program, Publication (Box 114, Folder 6)
  - Item 11: Your Department of Labor Its Organization and Services, Publication (Box 114, Folder 6)
  - Item 12: The United States Department of Laborand what it does, Publication (Box 114, Folder 6)
  - Item 13: The United States Department of Labor, Publication (Box 114, Folder 6)
  - Item 14: Hearing Before the Committee on Labor and Public Welfare United States Senate, Publication (Box 114, Folder 6)
    March 11. Item is in English.
  - Item 15: Introduction to Office Procedures For New Clerical Employees, Publication (Box 114, Folder 6)
  - Item 16: What You Should Know About the Pension and Welfare Law, Publication (Box 114, Folder 6)
  - Item 17: The Interview In Counseling An Outline of Interviewing Procedure for Use of Community Advisory Centers, Publication (Box 114, Folder 6)
  - Item 18: New Directions of the U.S. Employment Service, Publication (Box 114, Folder 6)
    October 11. Item is in English.
  - Item 19: Publications of the U.S. Department of Labor, Publication (Box 114, Folder 6)
  - Item 20: A Brief History of the Department of Labor, Publication (Box 114, Folder 6)
  - Item 21: Department of Labor, Federal Security Agency, and Related Independent Offices Appropriation Bill, Fiscal Year 1947, Publication (Box 114, Folder 6)
    June 11. Item is in English.
  - Item 22: Rules for the Conduct of the Hearing, Publication (Box 114, Folder 6)
    December 21. Item is in English.
  - Item 23: Challenge and Change a Brief History, Publication (Box 114, Folder 6)
  - Item 24: Performance Requirements and Evaluation, Publication (Box 114, Folder 6)
  - Item 25: Performance Rquirements and Evaluation, Publication (Box 114, Folder 6)
  - Item 26: A Guide to the National Labor Relations Act Procedures and Practices, Publication (Box 114, Folder 6)
    By Louis G. Silverberg. Item is in English.
  - Item 27: No.10 The Development of Collective Bargaining, Publication (Box 114, Folder 6)
  - Item 28: Profile of Unemployment, Publication (Box 114, Folder 6)
  - Item 29: The Unemployment Problem: What We Can Learn From European Experience, Publication (Box 114, Folder 6)
    By Robert J. Myers. April 20. Item is in English.
  - Item 30: The Anatomy of Unemployment, Publication (Box 114, Folder 6)
    By Ewan Clague. May 8. Item is in English.
  - Item 31: A Profile of Unemployment In the Early 1960's, Publication (Box 114, Folder 6)
    May 18. Item is in English.
  - Item 32: The Future Shape of the Labor Force, Publication (Box 114, Folder 6)
    By Ewan Clague. May 16. Item is in English.
  - Item 33: Major Economic Problems of the Future: Employment, Labor Force Growth, and Productivity, Publication (Box 114, Folder 6)
    By Ewan Clague. March 28. Item is in English.
  - Item 34: The Dimensions of the Employment Problem, Publication (Box 114, Folder 6)
    By Robert J. Myers. October 13. Item is in English.
  - Item 35: Development and Utilization of Manpower For Better Living Standards, Publication (Box 114, Folder 6)
    By Louis Levine. May 15. Item is in English.
  - Item 36: The Background of the Pension Problem, Publication (Box 114, Folder 6)
    By Ewan Clague. December 3. Item is in English.
  - Item 37: Manpower For Defense, Publication (Box 114, Folder 6)
    By Lewis D. Barton. October 13. Item is in English.
  - Item 38: Industrial Home-Work Legislation and Its Administration, Publication (Box 114, Folder 6)
  - Item 39: Conciliation Agreement Between U.S. Department of Labor Employment Standards Administration Office of Federal Contract Compliance Programs and Schering Corporation, Publication (Box 114, Folder 6)
  - Item 40: The Ethicon/ACTWU Work Involvement Process, Publication (Box 114, Folder 6)
- Box: 114, Folder: 7 (Box 114, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: New "Guides for Supervisors" Series - Guide #1, Position Management and Classification, Publication (Box 114, Folder 7)
    March 2. Item is in English.
- Box: 114, Folder: 8 (Box 114, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Settled Peacefully, Publication (Box 114, Folder 8)
  - Item 2: "Re-Tool Your Thinking" for your job tomorrow, Publication (Box 114, Folder 8)
  - Item 3: Where Do We Stand on Minimum Wage, Publication (Box 114, Folder 8)
    By Frieda S. Miller. April 23. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Opportunities For Negro Women In the Medical and Other Health Services, Publication (Box 114, Folder 8)
  - Item 5: Women In the 80th Congress, Publication (Box 114, Folder 8)
    September 15. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: The Interview In Counseling An Outline of Interviewing, Publication (Box 114, Folder 8)
  - Item 7: The United States Department of LaborToday, Publication (Box 114, Folder 8)
  - Item 8: Statement of James P. Mitchell, Secretary of Labor, Before the Special Subcommittee on Welfare and Pension Fund Legislation of the Senate Committee on Labor and Public Welfare, Publication (Box 114, Folder 8)
    By James P. Mitchell. May 27. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: The Length of Working Life, Publication (Box 114, Folder 8)
    By Seymour L. Wolfbein. July. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: Descriptions for Jobs Studied in Selected Metalworking Industries, Publication (Box 114, Folder 8)
  - Item 11: Responsibilities, Programs, Resources of the U.S. Department of Labor, Publication (Box 114, Folder 8)
  - Item 12: Older Worker Placement, Publication (Box 114, Folder 8)
    By Ewan Clague. December 5. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: Prices, Wages, and Productivity In the Postwar Period, Publication (Box 114, Folder 8)
    By Ewan Clague. September 23. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: The Federal Government's Interest in Health, Welfare and Pension Plans, Publication (Box 114, Folder 8)
    By Ewan Clague. December 12. Item is in English.
  - Item 15: Professional Placement Service of the United States Employment Service, Publication (Box 114, Folder 8)
  - Item 16: Audit Guide for Manpower Administration Contracts, Publication (Box 114, Folder 8)
  - Item 17: Change and Challenge In the Labor Force, Publication (Box 114, Folder 8)
    By James P. Mitchell. December 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 18: United States Department of Labor Fortieth Anniversary 1913-1953 Honor Awards Ceremony, Publication (Box 114, Folder 8)
    March 4. Item is in English.
- Box: 114, Folder: 9 (Box 114, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Hearing Before the Committee on Labor and Public Welfare United States Senate, Publication (Box 114, Folder 9)
    January 28. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Hearing Before the Special Subcommittee on Education of the Committee on Education and Labor House of Representatives, Publication (Box 114, Folder 9)
    May 15. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Your U.S. Department of LaborIts History and Its Aims, Publication (Box 114, Folder 9)
  - Item 4: The National Apprenticeship Program, Publication (Box 114, Folder 9)
  - Item 5: Arbitration of Grievances, Publication (Box 114, Folder 9)
  - Item 6: Planned Training, Publication (Box 114, Folder 9)
  - Item 7: Employment Service assistance to Government Agencies, Publication (Box 114, Folder 9)
  - Item 8: The National Apprenticeship Program, Publication (Box 114, Folder 9)
  - Item 9: The Right Job A Labor Department Guide For Returning Servicemen, Publication (Box 114, Folder 9)
  - Item 10: A layman's guide to basic law under the National Labor Relations Act, Publication (Box 114, Folder 9)
  - Item 11: Earnings and Standard of Living of 1,000 Railway Employees During the Depression, Publication (Box 114, Folder 9)
    By Carter Goodrich. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: Departments of Labor, and Health, Education, and Welfare, and Related Agencies Appropiation Bill, 168, Publication (Box 114, Folder 9)
    May 22. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: Bridge to Employment, Publication (Box 114, Folder 9)
  - Item 14: A Short History of the Department of Labor, Publication (Box 114, Folder 9)
  - Item 15: Hearings Before the Committee on Appropriations United States Senate, Publication (Box 114, Folder 9)
    February 7. Item is in English.
  - Item 16: Labor Offices in the United States and Canada, Publication (Box 114, Folder 9)
  - Item 17: Departments of Labor, and Health, Education, and Welfare, and Related Agencis Appropriation Bill, 1969, Publication (Box 114, Folder 9)
  - Item 18: The United States Department of Labor, Publication (Box 114, Folder 9)
  - Item 19: Your Department of Labor Its Organization and Srevices, Publication (Box 114, Folder 9)
  - Item 20: Employee Handbook, Publication (Box 114, Folder 9)
  - Item 21: Honor Awards, Publication (Box 114, Folder 9)
  - Item 22: Careers in the U.S. Department of Labor, Publication (Box 114, Folder 9)
  - Item 23: Regulations Governing Administration of the Federal Employees' Compensation Act, Publication (Box 114, Folder 9)
  - Item 24: Hearing Before the Committee on Labor and Public Welfare United States Senate, Publication (Box 114, Folder 9)
  - Item 25: A Short History of the Department of Labor, Publication (Box 114, Folder 9)
  - Item 26: A Short History of the Department of Labor, Publication (Box 114, Folder 9)
  - Item 27: The Department of Labor: Its History and Aims, Publication (Box 114, Folder 9)
  - Item 28: Your U.S. Department of Laborand what it does, Publication (Box 114, Folder 9)
  - Item 29: United States Department of Labor, Publication (Box 114, Folder 9)
  - Item 30: Cost Savings Through Standardisation-Simplification-Specialisation In The Clothing Industry, Publication (Box 114, Folder 9)
  - Item 31: Women In Radio, Publication (Box 114, Folder 9)
- Box: 115, Folder: 1 (Box 115, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: So You Have to Write a Position Description, Don't Worry It's not so bad millions have done it, Publication (Box 115, Folder 1)
  - Item 2: Here's How to Make Your Ideas and Effort Pay Off, Publication (Box 115, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: 101 Ways, Publication (Box 115, Folder 1)
    March 1965. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: The Commanding Officer's Annual Report to the Personnel of the Naval Supply Depot, Publication (Box 115, Folder 1)
  - Item 5: OIR Newsletter Vol. 7, No. 10, Publication (Box 115, Folder 1)
    October 1956. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Navy Beneficial Suggestions Digest Vol. 9, No. 3, Publication (Box 115, Folder 1)
    November 1956. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Department of the Navy OIR Notice 12087, Publication (Box 115, Folder 1)
    March 8, 1957. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Navy Civilian Personnel Instructions: NCPI Cover Sheet 627, Publication (Box 115, Folder 1)
    January 31, 1956. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Conference Sense, Publication (Box 115, Folder 1)
  - Item 10: Training of Office and Clerical Employees of the Naval Establishments: Suggestions for the Organization and Operation of Ivb Training Programs, Publication (Box 115, Folder 1)
  - Item 11: Navy Wage Administration: History and Legal and Administrative Framework, Publication (Box 115, Folder 1)
  - Item 12: Position Classification Handbook for Supervisors and Employees of the Naval Establishment, Publication (Box 115, Folder 1)
  - Item 13: Position Classification Handbook for Supervisors and Employees of the Naval Establishment, Publication (Box 115, Folder 1)
    July 1960. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: Position Management Standards, Publication (Box 115, Folder 1)
    September 1966. Item is in English.
  - Item 15: Wage Surveys in the General Wage Service, Publication (Box 115, Folder 1)
  - Item 16: Position Classification Handbook for Supervisors and Employees of the Naval Establishment, Publication (Box 115, Folder 1)
  - Item 17: Position Classification Handbook for Supervisors and Employees of the Naval Establishment, Publication (Box 115, Folder 1)
    July 1958. Item is in English.
  - Item 18: Incentive Awards: U.S. Naval Ordnance Plant: Louisville, Kentucky, Publication (Box 115, Folder 1)
    Revised 1956. Item is in English.
  - Item 19: Department of the Navy: Policies and Procedures for Wage Fixing, Publication (Box 115, Folder 1)
    June 1955. Item is in English.
- Box: 115, Folder: 2 (Box 115, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Eight Navy Civil Engineers, Publication (Box 115, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: Get Your Career off the Ground in Naval Aviation, Publication (Box 115, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: The Ready Reserve, Publication (Box 115, Folder 2)
  - Item 4: Advanced Electronics: The Navy, Publication (Box 115, Folder 2)
  - Item 5: Working for the USA: How to Apply for Civil Service Jobs, Publication (Box 115, Folder 2)
    December 1973. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: U.S. Navy Career Guide, Publication (Box 115, Folder 2)
  - Item 7: Eight Navy Civil Engineers, Publication (Box 115, Folder 2)
  - Item 8: Techniques for Conducting the Negotiating Conference, Publication (Box 115, Folder 2)
    March 1963. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: The Naval Reserve Veteran Program. A Unique part-time job., Publication (Box 115, Folder 2)
  - Item 10: The Submarine Service, Publication (Box 115, Folder 2)
  - Item 11: A Whole New World A Whole New Navy!, Publication (Box 115, Folder 2)
  - Item 12: Civilian Employment with the Department of the Navy, Publication (Box 115, Folder 2)
  - Item 13: Navy Civilian Engineers: Opportunity in Engineering, Publication (Box 115, Folder 2)
  - Item 14: A Future In Civilian Careers With Navy, Publication (Box 115, Folder 2)
  - Item 15: A Nuclear-Trained Naval Officer, Publication (Box 115, Folder 2)
  - Item 16: Ambassador of Good Will: A Link in Public Relations, Publication (Box 115, Folder 2)
  - Item 17: Employee Development Opportunities: Navy Department Bureau of Ordnance Civilian Personnel Branch, Publication (Box 115, Folder 2)
  - Item 18: Manual of Employment Interviewing, Publication (Box 115, Folder 2)
    September 25, 1957. Item is in English.
  - Item 19: Student Engineering Development Program, Publication (Box 115, Folder 2)
  - Item 20: How Federal Agencies Develop Management Talent, Publication (Box 115, Folder 2)
    April 1953. Item is in English.
  - Item 21: Training Guide for Mail and File Operations, Publication (Box 115, Folder 2)
    September 30, 1955. Item is in English.
  - Item 22: Training Your Staff: A Guide for Supervisors, Publication (Box 115, Folder 2)
    December 21, 1960. Item is in English.
  - Item 23: Speaking of Supervision, Publication (Box 115, Folder 2)
    By J. E. McKinnis. Item is in English.
- Box: 115, Folder: 3 (Box 115, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Apprentice Training in U.S. Naval Shipyards: Representative Schedules and Outlines, Publication (Box 115, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: U.S. Navy Manual of Safety Equipment, Publication (Box 115, Folder 3)
- Box: 115, Folder: 4 (Box 115, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: United States Safety Precautions, Publication (Box 115, Folder 4)
- Box: 115, Folder: 5 (Box 115, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Facts About United States Money, Publication (Box 115, Folder 5)
  - Item 2: The Treasury Story, Publication (Box 115, Folder 5)
- Box: 115, Folder: 6 (Box 115, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: 6 Point Nation-Wide Employment Program, Publication (Box 115, Folder 6)
  - Item 2: Mational Policies of the United States Employment Service: Effective for all State Employment Services, Publication (Box 115, Folder 6)
    September 1, 1953. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Guide to the Organization and Operationof Reemployment Offices, Publication (Box 115, Folder 6)
    July 22, 1933. Item is in English.
- Box: 115, Folder: 7 (Box 115, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: The Employee Evaluation Program: A Handbook for Rsting and Reviewing Officials, Publication (Box 115, Folder 7)
- Box: 115, Folder: 8 (Box 115, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: U.S. Federal Mediation and Conciliation Service: Statement of Arbitration Functions and Facilities, Publication (Box 115, Folder 8)
    May 17, 1948. Item is in English.
- Box: 115, Folder: 9 (Box 115, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Questionnaire on Personal Activities in the Federal Reserve Banks and their Branches, Publication (Box 115, Folder 9)
    April 7-10, 1920. Item is in English.
- Box: 115, Folder: 10 (Box 115, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Retirement System of the Federal Reserve Banks, Publication (Box 115, Folder 10)
    Ninth Revision: May, 1949. Item is in English.
- Box: 115, Folder: 11 (Box 115, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Getting Your Ideas Across Through Writing: Training Manual No. 7, Publication (Box 115, Folder 11)
  - Item 2: A Personnel Program: Training Manual No. 3, Publication (Box 115, Folder 11)
  - Item 3: Staff Development, The Supervisor's Job: Training Manual No. 6, Publication (Box 115, Folder 11)
  - Item 4: Suggestions Relating to the Preparaption of Instructional Materials for the Supplementary Training of Apprentices, Publication (Box 115, Folder 11)
  - Item 5: Federal Security Agency Social Security Administration Organization Chart, Publication (Box 115, Folder 11)
  - Item 6: Accounting Operations Division Resume of Operations, Publication (Box 115, Folder 11)
- Box: 115, Folder: 12 (Box 115, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Direct Investment Abroad and the Multinationals: Effects on the United States Economy, Publication (Box 115, Folder 12)
    By Peggy B. Musgrave, foreward by Senator Frank Church. August 1975. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Interim Staff Report of Activities of the Pension Study Task Force of the General Subcommittee on Labor, Publication (Box 115, Folder 12)
    April 1972. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Hearing before the Joint Committee on Printing Congress of the United States, Publication (Box 115, Folder 12)
    April 10, 1961. Item is in English.
- Box: 115, Folder: 13 (Box 115, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: A Strategy for Revolution that Never Ends, Publication (Box 115, Folder 13)
  - Item 2: Group Insurance Plan for Corporate and Group Employees, Publication (Box 115, Folder 13)
  - Item 3: Personal Accident Insurance Plan, Publication (Box 115, Folder 13)
- Box: 115, Folder: 14 (Box 115, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: Inter-American Bulletin Vol. 23, No. 1, Publication (Box 115, Folder 14)
    February 1963. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Inter-American Bulletin Vol. 23, No. 2, Publication (Box 115, Folder 14)
    April 1963. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Inter-American Bulletin Vol. 23, No. 3, Publication (Box 115, Folder 14)